## **KEVIN RIOS**

**FULL STACK DEVELOPER** 

#### **DETAILS**

PHONE

562-355-2256

**EMAIL** 

rioskevin89@gmail.com

LINKS

Website

<u>Github</u>

**Linkedin** 

**SKILLS** 

Node.js

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$ 

HTML & CSS

• • • • •

SQL

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$   $\circ$ 

HTML

• • • •

MySQL

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$ 

Git

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$ 

React

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$   $\circ$ 

JavaScript

• • • • 0

#### **PROFILE**

Passionate Full Stack Developer with a background in Web Development with 2 years of experience bringing forth the willingness to learn from others and the ability to adapt and excel in any environment. Seeking to use my experience to help my fellow developers and learn from them.

### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

## Web Developer, Kimo Wireless

Bellflower

Oct 2021 — Oct 2021

Freelanced for a cellphone repair shop and created them a landing page site for their shop. Worked closely with the owner to make sure he was satisfied with his website.

- · Effetively multitasked and worked well with the shop owner
- · Worked to assess competing websites in regards to content, look, and feel.
- Brought forth vast experience designing and developing responsive design websites.
- Effectively translated client requirements into application designs and system requirements.

## Web Developer, Dominguez Quality Upholstery

Carson

Nov 2020 — Nov 2020

Freelanced for an upholstery business to create them a modern responsive website where users can learn about their company

- Created a user-friendly experience that converted itself into more sells for the company
- Successfully designed what the client asked for and improved his business after the website went live.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor of Science, California State University, Dominguez Hills**

Carson

Jan 2017 — Present

Achieved the Deans List for every semester